DENYS KRYCHEVSKYI

CONTACTS —

+1 (206) 799-0080 📞

krychevskyidenys@gmail.com

3916 East Garfield St Seattle, WA 98112

https://www.linkedin.com/in/denys-krychevskyi-b00a6a166/

EDUCATION —

Bachelor's degree in Mining Engineering Dnipro University of Technology Dnipro, Ukraine, 2003-2008

> Graphic Design, HTML, CSS Training Center "Specialist" at the MSTU. NE Bauman Moscow, Russia, 2014-2015

PORTFOLIO -

https://denkportfolio.herokuapp.com

SKILLS -

Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
Acrobat
Acrobat Pit Stop Pro
Smart Stream Designer
HTML
CSS
MS Office
Excel

ADDITIONAL SKILLS —

Customer Service
Leadership
Communication
Teamwork
Decision-making
Time management

RECOGNITIONS —

Top performer recognition November 2018/Staples

HOBBY -

Basketball Hiking Healthy food cooking

PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Self-motivated and dedicated professional with leadership skills and well over 10 years of customer service experience. Energetic with expertise in print, packaging and marketing & advertising design, as well as advanced skills in Adobe Creative Suite, including Photoshop, Acrobat, Illustrator, and InDesign.

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGN SPECIALIST November 2017 - present day Digi Copy & Print, Seattle, WA

- \cdot Prepare unique print materials, including advertisements, brochures, and logo design.
- \cdot Contribute ideas during strategic and conceptual brainstorming sessions.
- \cdot Collaborate with a team to offer improvements and directions on the projects.
- · Design artistic signage for special corporate events.
- · Support production of various proposal volumes under tight time constraints.
- · Electronically prepare art and copy layouts for digital production to meet Customer specifications.
- · Work with Variable Data, Acrobat Pit Stop and Smart Stream Designer.
- · Generate Die Specification Drawings.

PRINT AND MARKETING SUPEVISOR | September 2018 - May 2019 Staples, Seattle, WA

- · Led multiple projects or tasks at a given time while under pressure to meet weekly deadlines and ensure customer satisfaction.
- · Delegated tasks to the members of design team and provided counsel on all aspects of the project.
- · Supervised the assessment of all graphic materials in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the project.
- · Trained new associates in the department.

PRINT AND MARKETING ASSOCIATE | November 2017 - September 2018 Staples, Seattle, WA

- · Assessed and provided copy and print solutions that exceed customer needs.
- Managed multiple priorities while providing consultative interaction, producing top quality finished products, and establishing the opportunities to build business with the customer.
- · Used print production software and professional printing equipment

STORE MANAGER | June 2012 - July 2017

Burylin Furniture Store, Moscow, Russia

- · Successfully managed and coordinated design projects from concept through completion.
- · Developed strong rapport and working relationship with team members.
- · Developed unique home and office-furniture design solutions.
- · Trained and guided personnel.
- · Identified customer needs and developed promotional offers.